frontify.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy - Frontify

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Frontify we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals: If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team. Frontify Inc. (“Frontify”) operates several websites including Frontify.com. It is Frontify’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. 

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Frontify collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Frontify’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Frontify’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Frontify may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. Frontify also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on the Frontify Blog. Frontify only discloses logged in user under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below. 

If you log in and comment through the Disqus service, Disqus receives state data and comment data. Disqus uses Personal Information for the following purposes: (i) internally to provide and improve their Site, services, features and content, (ii) to fulfill requests you may make to them, (iii) to personalize your experience and (iv) to provide you with information and offers from them or third parties that they believe you may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information on services and products offered by them or third parties. They may permit their vendors to access your Personal Information, but only in connection with services that they perform for them and not to use for their own purposes. They may share or transfer your Personal Information in connection with a merger, sale or reorganization of all or a part of their business. Lastly, they may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by process of law, or if necessary in order to investigate fraud, a violation of the Site Terms of Use or in connection with any harm being caused to a third party or their rights. They may use and disclose non-personal information for any number of reasons and with any number of third parties. Please note that Disqus may change its privacy policy, and verify the current privacy policy from the Disqus site. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Frontify’s websites choose to interact with Frontify in ways that require Frontify to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Frontify gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at Frontify.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Frontify – by purchasing a subscription to a Frontify service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Frontify collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Frontify. Frontify does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Aggregated Statistics

Frontify may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Frontify may monitor the total amount of projects, screens and other related entities created with our product . Frontify may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Frontify does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Frontify discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Frontify’s behalf or to provide services available at Frontify’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Frontify’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Frontify will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Frontify discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Frontify believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Frontify, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Frontify website and have supplied your email address, Frontify may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Frontify and our products. We primarily use our product blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Frontify takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

### Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. The tool uses "cookies," which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors' us of the webiste and to compile statistical reports on website activity for Frontify. 

We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information to our support team. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Frontify uses cookies to help Frontify identify and track visitors, their usage of Frontify website, and their website access preferences. Frontify visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Frontify’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Frontify’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

### Business Transfers

If Frontify, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Frontify goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Frontify may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Frontify may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Frontify’s sole discretion. Frontify encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
